Pavlos Papadopoulos | Front-End Web Developer



GitHub



LinkedIn



+306993751715



= mail



Thessaloniki, Greece

Front-End Web Developer, with industry experience building websites and web applications. Translate UX / UI designs to actual code. Ability to work on large projects. Can Deliver solutions using Jamstack architecture. Also, maintain updated knowledge of new trends and technology.

Experience _

Front-End Web Developer

DIGIBRIDGE GMBH

July 2021 - Present remote, Thessaloniki, Greece

Technologies:

- React.js / TypeScript / React Query / Storybook
- ➤ React Testing Library + Jest
- CSS (Sass)

Front-End Web Developer

EXEO LP

May 2019 – June 2021 Thessaloniki, Greece

Technologies:

- ➤ ASP.NET Core / DevExtreme UI components
- CSS (Sass) / Bootstrap
- JavaScript (jQuery, Knockout.js)

Freelance Web Developer

- > Building a website-blog for a medical professional
- Technologies: Next.js / Strapi headless CMS / Sass

Skills -

- HTML5 / CSS3 (Sass) / JavaScript (React.js / Next.js, Redux, jQuery, Knockout.js)
- ➤ Testing (React Testing Library / Enzyme)
- Bundlers (Webpack, Parcel)

Projects

- Order Management System (React.js / Redux / Jest / Enzyme)
- Portfolio Page (Next.js Netlify, Ghost headless CMS AWS)
- > React App (time machine) My article on dev.to

Education -

University of Thessaly - <u>MASTER'S DEGREE</u>: AUTOMATION IN AGRICULTURE **Aristotle University** - BACHELOR'S DEGREE: AGRICULTURAL ENGINEERING

2007 - 2012

1999 - 2006

Languages _

English: Cambridge First Certificate In English, Level B2 Spanish: State Certificate of Language Proficiency, Level B1